

🛘 +90 539 340 5527 | 🔀 molcaytercanli@gmail.com | 🍪 www.tercanli.com | 🖸 molcay | 🤡 molcay | 📓 molcay | 🛅 molcay | 🐚 molcay

# Summary .

I'm a Software Engineer at a start-up called Urla Digital Agriculture. I have **3+ years** experience specialising in the **full stack web development**, and I have experience on different cloud providers. I love \*nix based environments and enjoys to customise all of the development environment and automating stuffs. Also, I interested in devising a better **problem-solving methods** for challenging tasks, and **learning new technologies** for fun.

### Skills

**Programming** Python, JavaScript, Java, Scala

**Web** Django, Vue.js, React, Play, Flask, Spring **Others** Docker, GCP, AWS, Bash, Jenkins

Languages Turkish, English

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Urla Digital Agriculture

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER June 2020 - Present

• Developed a software for IoT devices that automate the controlled-environment agriculture

Tech stack: Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch, S3, SES, Timestream, Kinesis Fire-

**lech stack:** Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch, S3, SES, Timestream, Kinesis Fire hose)

Developed a dashboard to configure, update, and control IoT devices remotely
 Tech stack: Django (Python), MySQL, SQLite, Docker

**Linovi** Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER December 2017 - June 2020

Developed and maintained web services that serve as a chat bots (Jira, Asana, GitHub, Zendesk, Salesforce, Pagerduty) for Google Chat
 Tech stack: Play (Scala), React (Javascript), MySQL, Redis, Jenkins, Google Cloud Platform (like AppEngine, Compute Engine, Cloud Pub/Sub, Stackdriver)

- Developed a dashboard for an autonomous driving software company
  - Tech stack: Vert.x (Java), React (JavaScript), Amazon Web Services
- · Contributed a Software as a Service called Asena for an information security firm

Tech stack: Spring (Java), Angular.js (JavaScript), Flask (Python), Redmine

# **Projects**

### pyctx / django-pyctx

CORE MEMBER

- pyctx: Context package to pass data between function calls, use timers and log it. See more at https://github.com/molcay/pyctx
- **django-pyctx:** A django package to wrap pyctx and supply a middleware to trace and log incoming request and their flow. See more at https://github.com/molcay/django-pyctx

#### menusiparis.com

CORE MEMBER On Live

A Website to get the order from user with QR codes for restaurant, cafe. You can visit the website: https://menusiparis.com
 Tech stack: Django(Python), PostgreSQL

#### eczasis.com

Backend & Mobile On Development

A Web application to manage pharmacy stocks. You can visit the website: https://eczasis.com
 Tech stack: Django (Python), PostgreSQL, Kotlin (Android)

#### algari.com

Team Member Discontinued

 An e-commerce platform for Mugla Chamber of Commerce and Industry Tech stack: Django (Python), PostgreSQL

#### Rate'mall

TEAM MEMBER Senior Design Project on University

A global rating system for websites and users those want to create polls about anything. The system uses Elo Rating System to compare things.
 Tech stack: Django(Python), PostgreSQL

## **Education**

### Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University

Muğla, TURKEY

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

September 2012 - June 2017

- Rate'mall (Senior Design Project) for details please see section **Projects**
- **GPA:** 3.52 / 4.00

# **Extracurricular**

#### **COURSES**

2016, Nov Entrepreneurship Course, TÜBİTAK 2016, Feb Web Development with Django, AB2016 Muğla, TURKEY

Aydın, TURKEY

**COMPETITIONS** 

2017 KYK Siber Beyin Arıyor, 6th placed

Ankara, TURKEY

## **Certificates & Communities**

### CERTIFICATES

2017, Feb **Entrepreneurship Certificate**, TÜBİTAK

Muğla, TURKEY

2017, Jan CCNA R&S: Routing and Switching Essentials, Cisco Networking Academy

2016, Feb Web Development with Django, AB2016

Aydın, TURKEY

2016, Jan CCNA R&S: Introduction to Networks, Cisco Networking Academy

2015, Dec Introduction to Cybersecurity, Cisco Networking Academy